Guide to the New York University Archives Collection of Publications and Ephemera MC.334
New York University Archives
- RG 34.3. Center on Violence and Recovery, 2014-2015
  - Center on Violence and Recovery Facebook, May 2014-August 2015
    Facebook page for the Center on Violence and Recovery. The page contains links to posts about restorative justice, intimate partner violence, domestic violence, childhood trauma, and event descriptions.
- RG 35.0. Tisch School of the Arts, 1955-2017, 2023-ongoing
  - Calendar, 1980-2003 (Box 329, Folder 1-4)
  - DWP News, 1996-1997 (Box 329, Folder 5)
  - School of the Arts Newsletter, 1980-1984 (Box 329, Folder 6)
  - Polyphony, 1985 (Box 329, Folder 7)
  - Tisch School of the Arts Twitter, May 2014-May 2015
    Twitter Account of NYU Tisch School of the Arts. Tweets include alumni performances and awards, lectures, graduation ceremonies, Tisch Gala, Clive Davis Institute 10th Anniversary party, memorials, student performances, film screenings, job opportunities, parent and alumni days, and other events.
  - Tisch Class Notes, May 2023-ongoing
    Tisch Class Notes are short updates by Tisch School of Art alumni. Updates includes book and film releases, as well as other career updates. The page dates back to 2019.
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1955-2002 (Box 329, Folder 8-9, Box 330, Folder 1-9, Box 342, Folder 1)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- Posters, 1979-2009 (Box 167, Folder 12-13, Box 343, Folder 3)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 2000-2017, undated (Box 331, Folder 1-6, Box 332, Folder 1-7)
- RG 35.2. Interactive Telecommunications Program, 1978-2015
  - Interactions, 1988-1989 (Box 333, Folder 1)
  - Two-Way Cable Television... -- Final Report, 1978 (Box 333, Folder 2)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1980-1982, 2000-2015 (Box 333, Folder 3-4)
- RG 35.3. Dance Department / Theater Program, 1968-2007
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1968-2007 (Box 333, Folder 5-8, Box 334, Folder 1-8, Box 335)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- Posters, 2000-2005 (Box 344, Folder 1)
- RG 35.4. Broadcast Laboratory, 1972-1973
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- University Broadcast Lab Yearbook, 1972-1973 (Box 335, Folder 9, Box 336, Folder 1-6)
- RG 35.5. Department of Photography / Photography and Imaging, 1994-2019
  - Tisch School of the Arts Department of Photography and Imaging Blog, April 2014-April 2019
    Blog of the Department of Photography and Imaging at NYU Tisch School of the Arts. It includes activities from the students, faculty, and alumni of the program, as well as new of interest to the community. Blog posts focus on class offerings, community programs, exhibitions, conferences, public art, photographs, portraits, and other events. Posts date from April 2012 to July 2015.
  - Tisch School of the Arts Department of Photography and Imaging Facebook, May 2014-August 2015
    The Department of Photography & Imaging at Tisch is a four-year BFA program centered on the making and understanding of images. It includes posts of exhibitions, alumni news, student work, calls for papers, job postings, and other events.
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1998-2010 (Box 337, Folder 1)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- Senior Catalog, 1994, 2000-2003, 2006, 2010-2011, 2017 (Box 337, Folder 2-6, Box 338, Folder 1-4)
- RG 35.6. Institute of Film and Television / Cinema Studies / Film Program / Maurice Kanbar Institute of Film and Television, 1964-2019
  - Deep Focus, 1988 (Box 338, Folder 5)
  - Film and TV Today, 1997 (Box 343, Folder 4)
  - Film Review, 1998 (Box 338, Folder 6)
  - Maurice Kanbar Institute of Film and Television Cinema Studies Blog, May 2014-April 2019
    Blog for the Cinema Studies program at NYU. It contains alumni and department news, events, and student achievements. The blog dates back to 2009.
  - Maurice Kanbar Institute of Film and Television Facebook, May 2014-August 2015
    Facebook page for the Maurice Kanbar Institute of Film and Television. Facebook page contains posts related to moving to Los Angeles, grants and fellowships, production fund awards, Tony Hawkins Awards, film festivals and screenings, documentary distribution, networking, alumni advice and accolades, competitions, women in film, the animation program, and other events.
  - Maurice Kanbar Institute of Film and Television News, May 2014-April 2019
    Blog for the Maurice Kanbar Institute of Film and Television. Posts include information on events, film screenings and festivals, job opportunities, production grants, scholarships, alumni news, call for entries in festivals and other contests, and departmental announcements. The blog dates back to July 2011. The captures of the blog from 2016-2019 do not contain any content.
  - Maurice Kanbar Institute of Film and Television Twitter, May-August 2014
    Twitter feed for the Maurice Kanbar Institute of Film and Television.
  - Mirror, Mirror, 1990 (Box 338, Folder 7)
  - Phenakistoscope, 1971 (Box 338, Folder 8)
  - TMR Alumni Newsletter, 1964-1965 (Box 338, Folder 9)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1968-2012 (Box 339, Folder 1-5)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- Posters, 1970-1979, 2000-2006 (Box 343, Folder 4, Box 344, Folder 2)
- RG 35.7. Drama Department / Theater Program / Grad Acting Program, 1968-2015
  - Chronicle of the Performing Arts, 1978 (Box 339, Folder 6)
  - The Drama Review: TDR, 1968, 1972-1973, 1975-1976, 1979 (Box 339, Folder 7-8, Box 340, Folder 1-2)
  - Graduate Acting Program Facebook, May 2014-August 2015
    Facebook page of the Graduate Acting Program at NYU's Tisch School of the Arts. The page focuses on performances of Three Sisters, which opening night was cancelled due to an explosion on 2nd Avenue that brought down two buildings. Other posts include performances featuring NYU alumni.
  - Graduate Acting Program Twitter, May-July 2014
    Twitter Account of the Graduate Acting Program at NYU's Tisch School of the Arts. Tweets are mostly focused on NYU alumni Tony nominees.
  - Newsletter, 1979-1983 (Box 340, Folder 3)
  - Tisch Drama Twitter, May 2014-May 2015
    Twitter feed for the Tisch Drama department. Tweets include accolades for student presentations and performances, auditions, cast lists, theater recommendations in New York City, alumni performances, book talks, workshops, "This Week in Drama," DramaTalk presentations, artistic reviews, play writing, training, summer in the city program, and other events.
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1972-2007 (Box 340, Folder 4-9)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- Posters, 1981-1989 (Box 343, Folder 5)
- RG 35.8. Department of Performance Studies, 1981-1984, 2014-2019, undated
  - Performance Studies, 1983-1984 (Box 340, Folder 10)
  - Performance Studies Happenings, May 2014-April 2019
    Blog for the Performance Studies Department. Blog posts cover lectures, conferences, memorials, calls for papers, admissions information, book summaries, symposiums, awards, exhibits, performance announcements, and alumni news. The blog dates back to 2009. The captures of the blog from 2016-2019 do not contain any content.
  - Tisch School of the Arts Department of Performance Studies Facebook, May 2014-August 2015
    Facebook page for the Department of Performance Studies. Contains posts related to conferences, film screenings, lectures, writing workshops, PRAXIS conference, performances, Lenapehoking Transformance Laboratory,and admissions related content.
  - Tisch School of the Arts Department of Performance Studies Twitter, May 2014-May 2015
    Twitter feed for the Department of Performance Studies. Includes tweets from their alumni lecture series, the Performance Studies Community Conference (PRAXIS), listening salons, exhibits, Living Labor Conference, and other events.
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1981-1984, undated (Box 340, Folder 11)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- Posters, undated (Box 343, Folder 5)
- RG 35.9. Alternate Media Group, 1972-1974
  - Alternate Media Center, Summer 1972 (Box 342, Folder 2)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1972, 1974 (Box 341, Folder 1)
- RG 35.10. Department of Dramatic Writing, 2004
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 2004 (Box 341, Folder 2)
- RG 35.11. Department of Design for Stage and Film, 2002-2018
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 2002-2018 (Box 341, Folder 3)
- RG 35.12. Clive Davis Department of Recorded Music, circa 2003-2018
  - Clive Davis Department of Recorded Music Facebook, May 2014-August 2015
    Facebook page for the Clive Davis Institute of Recorded Music. Includes music recommendations, student and alumni music, music events, and course offerings.
  - Clive Davis Department of Recorded Music Twitter, May 2014-May 2015
    Twitter feed for the Clive Davis Institute of Recorded Music. Feed includes tweets related to music performances, workshops, internship opportunities, music reviews and recommendations, and music industry events.
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, circa 2003-2018 (Box 341, Folder 4)
- RG 35.14. TSOA Asia (Singapore), 2007
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 2007 (Box 341, Folder 5)
- RG 35.15. NYU Game Center, 2014-2015
  - NYU Game Center Facebook, May 2014-August 2015
    Facebook page for the NYU Game Center. Includes posts on gaming events, game industry events, lectures, indie games, gaming competitions, and student updates.
  - NYU Game Center Twitter, May 2014-May 2015
    Twitter feed for the NYU Game Center. Tweets include information on student created games, class offerings, Play Test Thursday, gaming competitions, employment in the game industry, and lectures on gaming.
- RG 35.16. Department of Musical Theater Writing, 2014-2015
  - Graduate Musical Theatre Writing Program Facebook, May 2014-August 2015
    Facebook page for the Graduate Musical Theatre Writing Program. Posts include faculty and alumni written performance listings.
  - Graduate Musical Theatre Writing Program Twitter, May 2014-May 2015
    Twitter feed for the Graduate Musical Theatre Writing Program. Tweets topics include events at New York theater venues, retweets from composers and alumni, awards, open mics, performance announcements, and job opportunities.
- RG 35.17. Tisch Initiative for Creative Research, 2022-ongoing
  - Tisch Initiative for Creative Research Newsletter, May 2022
    The Tisch Initiative for Creative Research (TCR) newsletter highlights recent and upcoming TCR activity as well as resource opportunities at NYU and in the field of performing, cinematic, and emerging media arts.
- RG 36.0. Gallatin Division, 1972-ongoing
  - Absolutely ABstract, 1996 (Box 341, Folder 6)
  - The 715 News, 1989-1992 (Box 341, Folder 7)
  - Gallatin Division Journal, 1978-1984 (Box 341, Folder 8-9)
  - Gallatin News, 1985-1987 (Box 341, Folder 10)
  - Gallatin Research Journal, 2011-2012 (Box 345, Folder 1)
  - The Gallatin Review, 1981-1996 (Box 345, Folder 2-7, Box 346, Folder 1-6, Box 347, Folder 1-5)
  - Gallatin School of Individualized Study Facebook, May 2014-August 2015
    Facebook page for NYU Gallatin. Facebook posts are related to the Gallatin Arts Festival, Confluence articles, alumni news, Gallatin photoshoot, Gallatin Galleries exhibits, Jazz festival, Gallatin Review, and other events.
  - Gallatin School of Individualized Study Twitter, May 2014-May 2015
    Twitter feed for NYU Gallatin. Tweets are related to alumni news and awards, lectures, Gallatin theater troupe, study abroad, admissions, Gallatin Arts Festival, Confluence, and other events.
  - Gallatin Today, 1992-2009, 2024-ongoing (Box 347, Folder 6-7, Box 348, Folder 1-2)
    Gallatin Today contains news, events, and essays written by and for the Gallatin alumni, faculty, students, and parents. The issues on the website date back to 2016.
  - The Literary Review, 2005-2011 (Box 348, Folder 3-5)
  - Mosaic, 2010 (Box 348, Folder 6)
  - School of the Earth, 2017 (Box 348, Folder 7)
  - University Without Walls Newsletter, 1973-1976 (Box 349, Folder 1)
  - Where I'm From, circa 2006 (Box 349, Folder 2)
  - The Writer at Work, 1981, 1983 (Box 349, Folder 3)
  - Writing on the Wall, 1976-1977 (Box 349, Folder 4)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1972-2014 (Box 349, Folder 5-8, Box 350, Folder 1-6, Box 351, Folder 1-5)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- Posters, 2003 (Box 343, Folder 6, Box 344, Folder 3)
- RG 36.2. Women's Studies Program, 1996-1997
  - Revolution/Evolution, 1996-1997 (Box 351, Folder 6)
- RG 36.3. Gallatin's Art Program, 1987-2008
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1987-1988, 2007-2008 (Box 351, Folder 7)
- RG 37.1. Center for War, Peace and the News Media, 1983-1992
  - American Press Coverage of Nuclear and Soviet Issues: A Bibliography, 1988 (Box 351, Folder 8)
  - Conference on War, Peace, and the News Media -- Proceedings, 1983 (Box 352, Folder 1)
  - Deadline, 1986-1992 (Box 352, Folder 2-4)
  - Occasional Paper, 1988 (Box 352, Folder 5)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1986-1992 (Box 352, Folder 6)
- RG 37.2. La Maison Française, 1956-2019
  - La Maison Française Facebook, May 2014-November 2018
    Facebook page for La Maison Française of NYU. It contains event listings and images from the events.
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1956-2019 (Box 352, Folder 7-8, Box 353, Folder 1-6, Box 354, Folder 1-5)
- RG 37.3. Deutsches Haus Goethe Institute, 1977-2018, undated
  - Deutsches Haus Facebook, May 2014-November 2018
    Facebook page for the Deutsches Haus at NYU. The pages includes information about German holidays, events at Deutsches Haus, images from events and exhibits, German word of the week, job opportunities, and language class offerings.
  - Deutsches Haus Twitter, May 2014-November 2018
    Twitter feed for the Deutsches Haus at NYU. Tweets topics include German events in New York, their conference on the 25th anniversary of "The Telephone Book" and the fall of the Berlin Wall, and German news.
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1977-2000, undated (Box 354, Folder 6, Box 355, Folder 1-2)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- Posters, 1989-1992 (Box 343, Folder 7)
- RG 37.4. New York Institute for the Humanities, 1978-2018, undated
  - Humanities Initiative Twitter, May 2014-May 2015
    Twitter feed for the Humanities Initiative at New York University. Contains links to events, tweets related to the Urban Humanities Symposium, reports on the state of the humanities, the Leadership Alliance Mellon Initiative, and book presentation videos.
  - New York Institute for the Humanities Journal, April 2014-May 2018
    New York Institute for the Humanities is a forum for promoting the exchange of ideas between academics, professionals, politicians, diplomats, writers, journalists, musicians, painters, and other artists in New York City. The journal page of the Institute contains descriptions of previous events, biographies of fellows, and news articles by and about fellows.
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1978-2000, undated (Box 355, Folder 3-4)
- RG 37.5. Center for International Studies / Center for International Relations, 1960-1991
  - Center for International Studies Policy Paper, 1960s (Box 355, Folder 5-6)
  - International Studies News, 1968-1973 (Box 355, Folder 7)
  - Journal of International Affairs, 1987-1988 (Box 356, Folder 1)
  - The World Observer, 1991 (Box 356, Folder 2)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1964-1969, 1974 (Box 356, Folder 3)
- RG 37.5.1. Center on International Cooperation (CIC): Project on International Courts and Tribunals (PICT), undated
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, undated (Box 356, Folder 4)
- RG 37.6. Center for Latin-American and Caribbean Studies, 1976-1998, 2014-ongoing
  - Center for Latin American and Caribbean Studies Blog, April 2014-ongoing
    Center for Latin American and Caribbean Studies Blog or Nexo Blog features articles that aim to increase visibility of Latin American and Caribbean-related issues and languages. The blog dates back to 2009.
  - LAPH Newsletter, 1978-1981 (Box 356, Folder 5)
  - Occasional Papers, 1976-1980 (Box 356, Folder 6)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1977-1998 (Box 356, Folder 7)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- Posters, 1981-1991 (Box 343, Folder 6)
- RG 37.7. Institute of Post-War Reconstruction / Institute of Economic Affairs, 1943-1960
  - After the War, 1943-1946 (Box 356, Folder 8)
  - Challenge, 1952, 1954-1960 (Box 356, Folder 9, Box 357, Folder 1-4)
  - Economic Affairs, 1946-1947 (Box 357, Folder 5)
- RG 37.8. Institute for Hebrew and Judaic Studies, 1962-1986
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1962-1986 (Box 357, Folder 6)
- RG 37.12. Institute of French Studies, 1977-2018
  - Institute of French Studies Twitter, May 2014-November 2018
    Twitter feed for the Institute of French Studies. The Twitter feed is mostly made up of French and European news, event reminders, welcome greetings to students and staff, and commendations for awards.
  - Liaison Newsletter, 1990 (Box 358, Folder 1)
  - Revue, 1991 (Box 358, Folder 2)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1977-2001 (Box 358, Folder 3-4)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- Posters, circa 1977-1992 (Box 343, Folder 8)
- RG 37.13. Center for French Civilization and Culture, 1979-2001
  - The Florence Gould Lectures at New York University, 1995-1996 (Box 358, Folder 5)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1979-2001 (Box 358, Folder 6-8)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- Posters, 1981-1991, 2001 (Box 343, Folder 9)
- RG 37.15. The Poetics Institute, 1977-1987
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1977-1987 (Box 359, Folder 1)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- Posters, 1981-1987 (Box 343, Folder 10)
- RG 37.16. American Institute for Verdi Studies, 1976-1979, 1991-2019
  The American Institute for Verdi Studies is America's leading research center for the life and works of Giuseppe Verdi. The AIVS was inaugurated at New York University in 1976.
  - American Institute for Verdi Studies Facebook, May 2014-May 2015
    Facebook page for the American Institute for Verdi Studies at New York University. Page contains information on their international conference Verdi's Third Century: Italian Opera Today, Verdi Forum, awards, exhibits, and other events related to Verdi.
  - Verdi Newsletter, 1976-1979 (Box 359, Folder 2)
  - VivaVerdi!, May 2014-April 2019
    VivaVerdi! is the newsletter produced by the American Institute for Verdi Studies. It provide news and information concerning scholarly activities, recent or forthcoming Verdi performances and recordings, updates on publication plans, calls for papers, and more.
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1976, 1991 (Box 359, Folder 3)
- RG 37.17. C.V. Starr Center for Applied Economics, 1974-1998
  - Abstract, 1978-1996 (Box 359, Folder 4-6)
  - C.V. Starr Center for Applied Economics Newsletter, 1978-1998 (Box 359, Folder 7-9, Box 360, Folder 1-2)
  - Discussion Paper Series, 1974 (Box 360, Folder 3)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1979-1990 (Box 360, Folder 4)
- RG 37.18. Albert Gallatin Associates, 1957-1991
  - The Gallatin Bulletin, 1975-1983 (Box 360, Folder 5)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1957-1991 (Box 360, Folder 6-7, Box 361, Folder 1-6, Box 362, Folder 1-7)
- RG 37.19. Ibero-American Language and Area Center, 1959-1976
  - Occasional Papers, 1973-1976 (Box 363, Folder 1-5)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1959-1976 (Box 363, Folder 6-7)
- RG 37.20. Urban Research Center, 1971-1972
  - Urban Notes, 1971-1972 (Box 363, Folder 8)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1971-1972 (Box 363, Folder 9)
- RG 37.21. Institute for Computer Research in the Humanities, 1965-1969
  - ICRH Newsletter, 1965-1969 (Box 364, Folder 1-3)
- RG 37.22. Samuel F.B. Morse Associates, 1985
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- Annual Dinner, 1985 (Box 364, Folder 4)
- RG 37.23. Catholic Center, 1950-1989
  - Catholic Center at NYU, 1987-1989 (Box 364, Folder 5)
  - Catholic Center Bulletin, 1972-1982 (Box 364, Folder 6)
  - Center, 1985, 1987-1989 (Box 364, Folder 7)
  - Newman, undated (Box 364, Folder 8)
  - Newman Newsletter, 1962-1966 (Box 364, Folder 9)
  - Voices of Newman Club of NYU, 1961 (Box 364, Folder 10)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1952-1987 (Box 364, Folder 11, Box 365, Folder 1-6)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera -- Posters, 1966 (Box 343, Folder 11)
- RG 37.24. Institute for Cultural Analysis, 1984-1987
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1984-1987 (Box 366, Folder 1)
- RG 37.25. Town Hall, 1935-1974
  - Calendar, 1966-1973 (Box 366, Folder 2)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1935, 1955-1974 (Box 366, Folder 3-6)
- RG 37.27. The Onassis Center for Hellenic Studies, 1987-1995
  - The Argonaut, 1995 (Box 366, Folder 7)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1987-1991 (Box 366, Folder 8-7)
- RG 37.28. Center for Applied Social Research, circa 1989
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, circa 1989 (Box 366, Folder 10)
- RG 37.30. Casa Italiana Zerilli-Marimo, 1990, 1999-2015
  - Casa Italiana Zerilli-Marimò Facebook, May 2014-August 2015
    Facebook page for the Casa Italiana Zerilli-Marimò. Posts are focused on music performances, photographs from events, book reviews, film screenings, Italy trips, fellowships, exhibits, Italian fashion, Italian occupation of Ethiopia, fundraising, and season highlights.
  - Casa Italiana Zerilli-Marimò Twitter, May 2014-May 2015
    Twitter feed for the Casa Italiana Zerilli-Marimò. Tweets topics include Italian Opera, exhibits, Italian Literature, panel discussions, Italian history, live tweets on Andre Leon Talley and fashion, and tourism.
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1990, 1999-2000 (Box 366, Folder 11-12)
- RG 37.31. NYC Consortium for European Studies, 1991
  - Europe / NYC, 1991 (Box 366, Folder 13)
- RG 37.33. King Juan Carlos I of Spain Center, 1983-2015
  - Calendar, 1999, 2004-2015 (Box 367, Folder 1-3)
  - King Juan Carlos I of Spain Center Facebook, May 2014-August 2015
    Facebook page for the King Juan Carlos I of Spain Center. The Facebook page contains links to their newsletter, events and exhibit listings, recommendations, and photographs from events.
  - News From the King Juan Carlos I of Spain Center, 1997, 2002 (Box 367, Folder 4)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1983-2008 (Box 367, Folder 5)
- RG 37.34. COPES: Conceptually Oriented Program in Elementary Science, 1969-1972
  - COPES Newsletter, 1970 (Box 367, Folder 6)
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1969-1972 (Box 367, Folder 7)
- RG 37.35. Center for Human Relations Studies, 1952-1955, undated
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1952-1955, undated (Box 367, Folder 8)
- RG 37.36. Iris and B. Gerald Cantor Film Center, 1997
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1997 (Box 367, Folder 9)
- RG 37.37. Glucksman Ireland House, 1993-2018
  - Calendar, 1999-2010, 2014-2015 (Box 367, Folder 10)
  - Glucksman Ireland House Facebook, May 2014-May 2015
    Facebook page for the Glucksman Ireland House. Website was not captured by crawler.
  - Glucksman Ireland House Twitter, May 2014-November 2018
    Twitter feed for the Glucksman Ireland House, which focuses on the Irish and Irish-American Studies. Includes tweets related to book launches, call for papers, traveling in Ireland, lectures, art exhibitions, admissions, film screenings, musical performances, the Ernie O'Malley Symposium, and other news and events relate to Ireland and Irish in America.
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1993-2015 (Box 367, Folder 11)
- RG 37.38. Remarque Institute, 2001-2011
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 2001-2011 (Box 368, Folder 1)
- RG 37.39. Lillian Vernon Center International Affairs, 1999-2002
  - Promotional Material and Ephemera, 1999-2002 (Box 368, Folder 2)
- RG 37.40. Alberto Vilar Global Fellows in the Performing Arts, circa 2002-2003